<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGauide</string>
    <string name="description">Description:</string>
    <string name="location">Location:</string>
    <string name="comments">Comments:</string>
    <string name="LocationKey">loc</string>
    <string name="NameKey">Name</string>
    <string name="DescKey">dec</string>
    <string name="RES_NAME">Resturants</string>
    <string name="HayatMall_name">HAYAT MALL</string>
    <string name="HayatMall_adress">King Abdul Aziz Road | the intersection with King Abdullah Road </string>
    <string name="HayatMall_desc">As soon as you take your first step into Hayat Mall, you will be surprised with the atmosphere combines comfort, shopping, fun, and peace.</string>
    <string name="SaharaMall_name">SAHARA MALL</string>
    <string name="SaharaMall_adress">King Abdulaziz Road, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia</string>
    <string name="SaharaMall_desc">Sahara Mall is well known to contain wide indoor pedestrian areas and spacious surrounding parking places.</string>
    <string name="KingdomMall_name">Kingdom Tower</string>
    <string name="KingdomMall_adress">King Fahad Road, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia </string>
    <string name="KingdomMall_desc">Besides the shopping mall, Kingdom Tower contains the Four Seasons Hotel Riyadh and apartments. There is a 56 m (184 ft) skybridge atop the skyscraper.</string>
    <string name="KingAbdullah_name">King Abdullah Park</string>
    <string name="KingAbdullah_adress">6628 Al Amin Abdullah Al Ali Al Naeem Street, Al Malaz، Al Malaz, Riyadh 12836</string>
    <string name="KingAbdullah_desc">Stretched out over 318,000 square meters, the new King Abdullah Malaz Park (KAMP) is the largest park of it’s kind in the Kingdom. Located in the Al-Malaz District near Prince Faisal bin Fahd Stadium, the park literally is a breath of fresh air!</string>
    <string name="SalamPark_name">SALAM Park</string>
    <string name="Salam_adress">Salam St, Salam, Riyadh 12651\n" </string>
    <string name="Salam_desc">The Salam Park in Riyadh is considered to be one of the biggest parks in the city and is an ideal location for people looking to spend some quality time with family and kids.</string>
    <string name="Rawdah_name">RAWDAH Park</string>
    <string name="Rawdah_adress">King Fahad Road, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia\n" </string>
    <string name="Rawdah_desc">The green landscapes are a place for tranquility and relaxation. Yet a meeting place for friends –a community center with a family atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="Najdiay_name">Al-Najdiyah Village</string>
    <string name="Najdiya_adress">AboBakr AlSiddeeq Street | Al Nuzhah Area, Riyadh 11464, Saudi Arabia\n </string>
    <string name="Najdiyah_desc">Serving Lebanese and American food, Al-Najdiyah Village is a favourite restaurant with tourists in Riyadh. Diners relax on large cushions on the floor, and enjoy traditional Nadji dishes in an authentic Bedouin atmosphere. The restaurant is open to women and families on Fridays only, so booking ahead for those days is essential.</string>
    <string name="MAMANORA_name">MAMA NOURA</string>
    <string name="MAMANORA_adress">Abdul Aziz Bin Museod Bin Julowi Street | District Al-Rahmaniyah\n </string>
    <string name="MAMANORA_desc">Serving Lebanese and American food, Al-Najdiyah Village is a favourite restaurant with tourists in Riyadh. Diners relax on large cushions on the floor, and enjoy traditional Nadji dishes in an authentic Bedouin atmosphere. The restaurant is open to women and families on Fridays only, so booking ahead for those days is essential.</string>
    <string name="National_name">National Museum of Saudi Arabia</string>
    <string name="National_adress">King Salman str.</string>
    <string name="National_desc">The National Museum of Saudi Arabia is a major national museum in Saudi Arabia. Established in 1999, it is part of the King Abdulaziz Historical Centre in Riyadh.</string>
    <string name="Abdulaziz_name">King Abdul Aziz Historical Centre</string>
    <string name="Abdulaziz_adress">King Faisal Road, Al Murabba, Riyadh 12631</string>
    <string name="Abdulaziz_desc">The King Abdul Aziz Historical Centre is a region in the city of Riyadh, the capital of Saudi Arabia. It is not the \"historic center\" of the city as this lies to the south around Masmak fort and the main Friday Mosque\" in the Dira district. </string>
    <string name="Masmak_name">Masmak Citadel</string>
    <string name="Masmak_adress">Al Futah Riyadh 12632 3471 Al Batha, Al Futah, Riyadh 12632 3471</string>
    <string name="Masmak_desc">The Masmak is a clay and mud-brick fort, with four watchtowers and thick walls, founded on stone blocks, lying in the center of Riyadh, in the old quarters.</string>
</resources>
